THEODOXA DAVADINATA

DATA SCIENTIST

theodoxa.dava@gmail.com

+628 5158 5872 55

LinkedIn

Profile Summary

I am a student of **Informatics Engineering** at the Satya Wacana Christian University. I am very interested in extracting knowledge or information from data. Campus experience provides a basic understanding of **Pyhon**, **Rapidminer**, **Oracle**, **RStudio**, **HTML**, **CSS** and **PHP**. Then I developed my skills further by taking training from TalentClass, especially Advanced **Excel** and **SQL** preprocessing.

Skill

- Python
- Rapid miner
- RStudio
- SQL
- Bootstrap

- HTML, CSS, PHP
 - Oracle
- Excel (Advance)
- Codelgniter
- Laravel

Project Experience

Personal Portofolio Website

• Build Website with Bootstrap

Comparison of Classification Methods on Iris Datas with Naive Bayes Classifier

Nov 2022

Nov 2022 - Now

- Designing Four Model of Naive Bayes Classifier.
- Compare the results of the accuracy of the four models using Naive Bayes Classifier. The highest accuracy is the best model when compared to other models

Analysis and Clustering of Customer ID with the Most Purchases Using the K-Mean June 2022 Algorithm on UK-Based Online Retail Data (Kaggle)

- Cleaning dirty datas in RapidMiner (such as empty value data, and incorrect data types)
- Designing data with the *K-Means Clustering* model, then evaluating the results of the model design. To know which model is better.

Artificial Intelligence - Handwritten Text Recognition

April 2022

- Using TensorFlow with Python
- Create a program that can recognize handwritten text.

Assistant Lecturer of Statistic and Probability

January 2020 - April 2020

• Teach a Student Informatics Engineering in Faculty of Information Technology in Statistics and Probability Course

Education

Satya Wacana Christian University

2019 - Now

Informatic Engineering

Licence & Certification

Python for Data Science (Cognitive Class)
R for Data Science (Cognitive Class)
Database Design and Programming With SQL
Latihan Dasar Kepemimpinan Mahasiswa
Latihan Menengan Kepemimpinan Mahasiswa
Latihan Lanjut Kepemimpinan Mahasiswa

February 2022

June 2022

2021

February 2020

May 2022

November 2022